Isolokwu Esther Ogechukwu 52, Bolaji Banwo Street, Surulere, Lagos State, Nigeria.

(+234) 08033002158

estherisolokwu@hotmail.com

PROFILE

A graduate of Surveying & Geoinformatics, Federal Polytechnic Idah. Equipped with a diligent and hardworking orientation, an unending quest for knowledge, an experienced team worker with a demonstrated history of leadership and effective communication skills.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

Higher National Diploma (Surveying and Geoinformatics)

Federal Polytechnic Idah, Kogi State

Dec 2016 – Oct 2019

(Upper credit)

National Diploma (Surveying and Geoinformatics)

Federal Polytechnic Idah, Kogi State

Nov 2013 – Feb 2016

(Upper credit)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2020 - Nov 2020

Graduate Intern (PISCES OFFSHORE LIMITED)

- Offshore Positioning (HYPACK)
- Mobilized Equipment for offshore Jobs.
- Processed subsea data (HYPACK, Global Mapper & Surfer)
- Generated contours and wireframe using SURFER
- Drew plans using AutoCAD

2017 - 2018

Vice President Nigerian Institution of Surveying Students, (2017/2018 session)

Federal Polytechnic Idah Chapter, Class of 2018

- Created a good communication link between my course mates and our lecturers
- · Organized tutorials on difficult courses each semester
- Organized revision classes for each course before exams

March 2015 - June 2015

Intern (WATERGATE TECHNICAL SERVICES LIMITED)

- Performed offshore positioning and surveys
- Performed Routine Maintenance of Survey Equipment.
- Mobilized Equipment for offshore Jobs.
- Processed subsea data

2013 - 2015 Treasurer Volunteer (LEGION OF MARY)

- Delivered mails and correspondence
- Prepared monthly financial reports and balancing of account
- Performed setup of alterwork

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Acquired skills Proficient in Hypack, Global Mapper, Surfer, ArcGIS, AutoCAD,

HTML, CSS, Microsoft Office packages, Basic Programming skills,

Administrative and Leadership skills.

Hobbies Photography, Reading, Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Arts and

Crafts, Graphic Design.

Referees Available upon request.

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIP

• Student Member, Nigerian Institution of Surveying Students (NISS).